Harold Stein Filk Collection
Harold Stein Filk Archive
Harold Stein Filk Collection
1960-2020
Harold Stein Filk Archive
filk
34 boxes and an unknown number of terrabytes
Harold Stein was an active member of the Filking community. He amassed a large collection of filk songs, zines, convention papers, and audio recordings.
Scope and Content
The Harold Stein Filk Collection contains....
Access
The collection is open and available for research.
Filk Music
- Audio
  - Live Performance
    - Concert
    - Filk Circle
    - Performance Circle
    - Notes/Set Lists
      - Dark Deeds & Desperate Men (and Women), Notes: So many j-cards for Dark Deeds Origin: Floating Filk Studios; Many, many, lots copy; genreform: j-card for CD (Box 15)
        j-card for CD
      - J-card for Wolves & Changelings, 1999; 1 copy; Notes: Black and white j-card with all lyrics for songs. Origin: Marchwood Media; genreform: j-card for tape (Box 14)
        j-card for tape
      - Mercedes Lackey Live!, 4 copy; Notes: Four signed mint condition original j-cards for Misty Lackey Live! Origin: Firebird Arts & Music of Oregon, Inc.; genreform: j-card for tape (Box 14)
      - Mythical Beasts Undubbed, 1 copy; Notes: Blue j-card with black printing, unfolded, mint condition. All song lyrics printed on card. Origin: Marchwood Media; genreform: j-card for tape (Box 14)
      - Set list and instructions to sound crew from Talis, 1 copy; Notes: Two handwritten pages with the set list and instructions to soundcrew: Set includes 1. Finding of the Feather 2. Archetype Cafe, 3. Cecilia's Face 4. Queen of Spindles 5. Spoon 6. Still Catch the Tide 7. Lady Moon 8. Ten Years 9. Belling the Cat 10. Steps of St. Paul's 11. Eleanor Roosevelt's Knitting 12. Corn Jenny. Other performers include Betsey and Kade Tinney, Dave Clement and Jeri-Lynn Cornish Origin:; genreform: Set list (Box 14)
        Set list
      - Set list for a Brenda Sutton concert, 1 copy; Notes: Set list includes, High Fantasy, Women with Drums, Un Chanson, Sex After C-Pap, I Knew A Guy Once, Serenity, These Two, Inner Seasons, Drinking With the Man in the Moon, Vor, Cruiser Dreaming, In a Gown Too Blue, Blue Spell, Journeys, Stray Dog Man, performers include Bill Sutton, Dave Clement, Vixy, Riverfolk (Chas and Becca), Tony Fabris, Betsey Tinney Origin:; genreform: Set list (Box 14)
      - Performers, possibly for a Betsey set based on the song names, Possibly Conflikt, unknown year, found with papers from Conflikt 7; 1 copy; Notes: Probably from a Conflikt Origin: Convention: Possibly Conflikt, unknown year, found with papers from Conflikt 7; genreform: List of Performers (Box 9)
        Convention -- Possibly Conflikt, unknown year, found with papers from Conflikt 7; List of Performers
    - Eclecticon Raw Joey Shoji @ FKO 2002 (minidisc from Dave W.), 2006; Eclecticon 2006; FilkOntario 2002; Dave Weingart (?) minidisc recording; 1 copy; Notes: Origin: Dave Weingart (?) minidisc recording Convention: Eclecticon 2006 and FKO 2002; genreform: Burnt CD (Box 4)
      Convention -- EclectiCon (2006); Convention -- FilkONtario 12 (2002); CD -- Burnt
    - Howard Scrimgeour Live at Anticipation, 2009; Scimgeour, Howard; Worldcon. Anticipation (67: 2009); 1 copy; Notes: Origin: Recorded live at Anticipation, the 67th World Science Fiction Convention, Montreal, Quebec, Canada, August 8, 2009 Convention: Anticipation the 67th World Science Fiction Convention 6-10 August, 2009; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 3)
      Convention -- WorldCon 67. Anticipation (2009); CD -- Commercial
  - Digital Media
  - Physical Media
    - Alexander James Adams
      - What Are We Doing?, 2010; Adams, Alexander James; Sea Fire Productions, Inc.; 1 copy; Notes: No liner notes, just a jewel case. Case may be elsewhere Origin: @2010 Sea Fire Productions, Inc. SFP-1020-2; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 6)
        CD -- Commercial
      - The Heros of Our Days, Canticles, the Soundtrack: Aria I, 2016; Adams, Alexander James; Sea Fire Productions, Inc.; 1 copy; Origin: © Copyright - Alexander James Adams / Sea Fire Productions (888295481373); genreform: Commercial CD (Box 5)
    - Aisling
      - The Pilgrim's Road, Aisling; Recorded and Engineered by Craig Markley at Lone Raven Studios, Delaware, OH, Digital Mastering: Trevor Sadler, Master Mind Productions, Producer: Andi Wolfe.; 1 copy; Notes: Mary Bertke was a member of this band and contributed vocals and an original jig The Spirit of the House to the album. Origin: Recorded and Engineered by Craig Markley at Lone Raven Studios, Delaware, OH, Digital Mastering: Trevor Sadler, Master Mind Productions, Producer: Andi Wolfe.; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 3)
      - Harp of Light, 2011; Aislinn; Recoded, mixed and mastred by Anne Prather at Star Rose Arts Studio Seattle, Washington (P) 2011 Anne Harlan Prather; 1 copy; Notes: Star Rose Arts CD-011-02 Origin: Recoded, mixed and mastred by Anne Prather at Star Rose Arts Studio Seattle, Washington (P) 2011 Anne Harlan Prather; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 6)
    - Heather Alexander
      - Wanderlust, 1994; Alexander, Heather; Sea Fire Productions, Inc.; 1 copy; Origin: @1994 Sea Fire Productions; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 3)
      - Life's Flame, 1996; Alexander, Heather; 1 copy; Origin: Recorded live, July 1996; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 3)
      - Musical Me, 2003; Alexander, Heather; Sea Fire Productions, Inc.; 1 copy; Origin: @2003 Sea Fire Productions; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 3)
      - Everafter, Alexander, Heather; Sea Fire Productions, Inc.; 1 copy; Notes: This album, like all of Heather's other albums is cursed against duplication Origin: Sea Fire Productions, Inc. (BMI) www.heatherlands.com; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 3)
      - Midsummer, Alexander, Heather; Sea Fire Productions, Inc.; 1 copy; Origin: Sea Fire Productions, Inc. (BMI) www.heatherlands.com; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 3)
      - WinterTide, Alexander, Heather; Adams, Alexander James; Sea Fire Productions, Inc.; 1 copy; Notes: Made during Alec's transition, clever use of multitracking to capture both sets of vocal qualities. Origin: Sea Fire Productions, Inc. (BMI) www.heatherlands.com; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 3)
    - Andrew Allen
      - Smooth Federation: A Star Trek Jazz Tribute by Andrew Allen, 2012; Allen, Andrew; Produced by Coverville Records; 1 copy; Origin: Produced by Coverville Records; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 6)
    - Rebecca Angel
      - Fantasy Escape, 2006; Angel, Rebecca; 1 copy; Origin: Copyright 2006; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 3)
    - Annwn
      - Anarchy and Rapture, 1997; Annwn; Elf Hill Music & Mayhem; 1 copy; Origin: @1997 Elf Hill Music & Mayhem; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 3)
    - Avalon Rising
      - Avalon Rising, 1995; Flowinglass Music @1995; 1 copy; Origin: Flowinglass Music @1995; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 3)
    - Baldbox
      - The Dumb Album, 2009; Chris Mezzolesta; 1 copy; Origin: Written, recorded, and produced by Baldbox, mostly over a weekend. Mastered by Chris Mezzolesta; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 6)
    - Rob Balder
      - Rich Fantasy Lives, Balder, Rob; 1 copy; Origin: rob balder dot com; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 3)
    - Banish Misfortune
      - Stronger Than Tea: The Sampler, 2003; Banish Misfortune; Whiskey: it's not just for breakfast any more.; 1 copy; Origin: @2003 Whiskey: it's not just for breakfast any more.; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 3)
    - Chris Benders
      - Still and All, Benders, Chris; 1 copy; Origin: Chris Benders' card is attached to the jewel case.; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 6)
    - Beth Kinderman & The Player Characters
      - Winter Is Coming, 2011; Beth Kinderman & the Player Characters; Beloved Porcupine Music; 1 copy; Origin: Beloved Porcupine Music; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 5)
    - Danny Birth
      - Otter Teas, 2012; Birt, Danny; 1 copy; Origin: DannyBirt.com; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 6)
    - Jeff and Maya Bohnhoff
      - I Remember the Rain, 2016; Bohnhoff, Jeff; Bohnhoff, Maya; Mystic Fig Studios; 1 copy; Origin: Mystic Fig Studios; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 5)
      - I Remember the Rain, 2016; Bohnhoff, Jeff; Bohnhoff, Maya; Mystic Fig Studios; 1 copy; Origin: Mystic Fig Studios; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 5)
      - Sullen - Reflections, Boldish, Misty; 1 copy; Origin: Misty Boldish; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 5)
      - Grated Hits, Bohnhoff, Maya; Bohnhoff, Jeff; Mystic Fig Studios; 1 copy; Origin: Mystic Fig Studios; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 3)
      - 3 Songs by Mattie, 2000; Brahen, Marilyn "Mattie"; 1 copy; Notes: Arrangment & Instrumentals by Larry McHugh Origin: Mattie Brahen; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 6)
    - Brobdingnagian Bards
      - Christmas in Brobdingnag Vol 1, 2006; Brobdingnagian Bards; Mage Records; 1 copy; Origin: Mage Records; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 5)
      - Bard Bootlegs, Vol. 1, 2001/2002; Brobdingnagian Bards; 1 copy; Notes: Signed by Marc Gunn and Andrew McKee Origin: Recordings are listed as June 29, 2001 and November 15, 2002 on the jcard. Recorded Live at KEOS 89.1 FM in Bryan, Texas on Celtic Core, Hosted by Tom Schwerdt CD-ROM featuring bootleg-quality MP3s record live. (sic) Mage Records, PO Box 4067, Austin, TX 78765; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 3)
      - A Faire to Remember, Brobdingnagian Bards; 1 copy; Origin: The Brobdingnangian Bards are Marc Gunn - Autoharp Andrew McKee - Recorder, Mandolin; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 3)
      - Nagians Only, Vol. 1, Brobdingnagian Bards; Mage Records; 1 copy; Notes: Signed "Wow, blast from the past" by Marc Gunn. Also signed by Andrew McKee with a mark under his name that resembles a twisted x. Origin: Distrubuted by MP3.com, Mage Records, PO Box 650128, Austin, Texas, 78765; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 3)
      - Songs of Ireland for St. Patrick's Day, Brobdingnagian Bards; 1 copy; Notes: Signed by Andrew McKee and Marc Gunn, Produced for MP3.com Origin: The Bards are ... Marc Gunn - Autoharp & Vocals, Andrew McKee - Recorder, Mandolin & Vocals, Mage Records, PO Box 650128 Austin, TX 7865; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 3)
      - Brobdingnagian Fairy Tales, 2005; Brobdingnagian Bards; 1 copy; Notes: Signed by Marc Gunn Origin: Copyright 2005 Marc Gunn & Andrew McKee; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 3)
    - Broceliande
      - Sir Christemas: Songs of the Season, 2001; Broceliande; Flowing Glass Music 2821 Truman Avenue, Oakland, CA 94605; 1 copy; Origin: @2001 Flowing Glass Music 2821 Truman Avenue, Oakland, CA 94605; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 3)
      - Gathering May: Songs of the Season, 2003; Broceliande; Flowinglass Music, 2821 Truman Avenue, Oakland, CA 94605; 1 copy; Origin: @2003 Flowinglass Music, 2821 Truman Avenue, Oakland, CA 94605; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 3)
    - Brooke Vs. John
      - Steel Cage Match, Brooke Vs. John; All tracks engineered and produced by Tony Fabris at Monkey Brains Studios, Seattle, Washington,; Album mastered by John McCaig at panicStudios in Seattle, Washington; 1 copy; Notes: Insert mentions all details that aren't on the case. Origin: All tracks engineered and produced by Tony Fabris at Monkey Brains Studios, Seattle, Washington, Album mastered by John McCaig at panicStudios in Seattle, Washington; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 6)
      - Geek Mythology, 2010; Brooks, Eben; 1 copy; Origin: All songs recorded using Apple Garage Band. All vocals by Eben Brooks, except where stated otherwise, Original lyrics and music copyright 1987-2010 by Eben Brooks, except where otherwise specified, cover design copyright @2010 by Eben Brooks, Starfield photo by Chensiyuan.; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 3)
      - Things with Wings, Brown, Carolyn; USB Studios; 1 copy; Notes: Many, many thanks to Ken Lalonde, and Peggi Warner-Lalonde at USB studios. You have helped a dream become reality. Also I am grateful to the Toronto area filk community. You are a great group of people, and I am so happy to claim you as friends. Finally, thanks to my family, human, feathered and furry, for your love and support. Origin: USB Studios; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 3)
      - Water Over the Bridge, Bucklin, Nate; Louie Spooner Bucklin; Curious Manor; 1 copy; Origin: Produced at Curious Manor by Louie Spooner Bucklin; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 3)
    - Captain Zorikh
      - The Three Chord Monte Strikes Again 1.5 With special guests: The Death Star Repairmen, 2008; Captain Zorikh; 1 copy; Origin: Zorikh Lequidre; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 6)
      - Three Chord Monte, Captain Zorikh; 1 copy; Notes: Rockabily and beyond! www.captainzorikh.com 917-865-1214 (This was probably purchased at a Lunacon) Origin: Self recorded; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 3)
    - Cats Laughing
      - Another Way to Travel, 2016; Cats Laughing; Beyond Conventions LLC; 1 copy; Origin: re-release @2016 Beyond Conventions LLC; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 5)
      - Reissue, 2016; Cats Laughing; 1 copy; Notes: A reissue of their tape as a CD, it has a cover that looks like a tape case flattened upside-down into the CD box. Origin: 2016 ReIssue; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 5)
    - Cheshire Moon
      - The Midnight Contingent, 2017; Cheshire Moon; 1 copy; Origin: Cheshire Moon; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 5)
      - Bonus Tracks and Outtakes, Cheshire Moon; 0 copy; Notes: No CD in case! Origin: Cheshire Moon; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 6)
      - Ways of Wind and Water, Cheshire Moon; Righteous Dog Recording; Norman, Isaac; The Record Mill in Ames; Mastered by Donna Miller at the Record Mill in Ames.; 1 copy; Notes: Signed on the back by all members of the band. Origin: Recorded at Righteous Dog Recording under the watchful eye and ear of Isaac Norman & with additional recording at The Record Mill in Ames Mixed and Mastered by Donna Miller at the Record Mill in Ames.; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 6)
    - Ariel Cinii
      - D'al Thyann (And it goes like this ...), 2012; Cinii, Ariel; Floating Filk Studios; 1 copy; Notes: Includes a chart of Abby's Sarine alphabet. Origin: Floating Filk Studios; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 6)
    - Chris Conway
      - Alien Salad Abduction, 2002; Conway, Chris; A New Day Records; 1 copy; Origin: @2002 Chris Conway A New Day Records; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 3)
    - Kari Maaren, Leslie Hudson and Devin Melanson
      - Pirate Elves in Space, 2013; Copy Red Leader; Maaren, Kari; Iocane Power; SOCAN; The Pond Studio, Southern, Ontario; 1 copy; Notes: Compilation CD of Kari Maaren, Leslie Hudson and Devin Melanson Origin: @2013 SOCAN Recorded, mixed, and mastered at The Pond Studio, Southern, Ontario; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 6)
    - Court & Country
      - Journey Through Time, Court & Country; 1 copy; Origin:; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 5)
      - Twelve Good Measures, Crime and the Forces of Evil; 1 copy; Notes: Plastic wrapped, it would appear, by hand. Origin: Crime and the Forces of Evil; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 5)
    - Mary Crowell
      - Scattering Seeds on the Pomegranate Tour, 2016; Crowell, Mary, Dr.; 1 copy; Origin: Mary Crowell in-print (unknown version/edition): http://www.magnusretail.com/merch.html; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 5)
    - Carrie Dahlby
      - Happy Ranch, 2007; Dahlby, Carrie; 1 copy; Notes: www.carriedahlby.com Origin: @2007 Carrie Dahlby; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 3)
    - Heather Dale
      - Call The Names, 2001; Dale, Heather; Chis Evans, Jason MacNeill. All songs written by Heather M. Dale (SOCAN) copyright @ Amphisbaena Music, 1993-2001.; Produced and Engineered by Heather Dale Additional Engineering by Chis Evans, Jason MacNeill. All songs written by Heather M. Dale (SOCAN) copyright @ Amphisbaena Music, 1993-2001.; 1 copy; Origin: Produced and Engineered by Heather Dale Additional Engineering by Chis Evans, Jason MacNeill. All songs written by Heather M. Dale (SOCAN) copyright @ Amphisbaena Music, 1993-2001.; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 3)
      - Heather Dale Live in Montreal, 2007; Dale, Heather; 1 copy; Notes: Recorded live to two-track digital by Steve Goldstein at The Yellow Door Coffeehouse (Montreal, Canada) Produced, mixed and mastered by Heather Dale &Ben Deschamps, The Finishing Room, Toronto Origin: Concert recording - 8 Dec 2007 / 8 July 2008; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 6)
      - Heather Dale Live in Koln, 2008; Dale, Heather; 1 copy; Notes: Recorded live to two-track digital by Chris Arndt at Em drugge Pittner (Venloer Str. 416 50823 Koln, Germany) Mixed and mastered by Dave MacKinnon, The Junkshop, Toronto. Produced by Heather Dale & Ben Deschamps. Origin: Concert recording - 31 May 2008; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 6)
      - The Green Knight, 2009; Dale, Heather; Amphis Music; 1 copy; Origin: Amphis Music, 5 Mariner Terrace, Suite 303, Toronto, ON M5V 3V6; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 6)
      - The Hidden Path, Dale, Heather; Amphis Music; 1 copy; Origin: Amphis Music; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 3)
    - Dandelion Wine
      - The Face on Mars, Dandelion Wine; AFK Studios (Tom Jeffers); 1 copy; Origin: AFK Studios (Tom Jeffers); genreform: Commercial CD (Box 2)
    - Katie Lynn Daniels
      - Through Space and Time, 2015; Daniels, Katie Lynn; 1 copy; Origin: @Katie Lynn Daniels; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 5)
    - Deutsche Harmonia Mundi
      - Early Music Sampler, 1993; Deutsche Harmonia Mundi; BMG Classics; 1 copy; Origin: BMG Classics; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 6)
    - Dust Rhinos
      - Got Guinness?, Dust Rhinos; 1 copy; Origin: Dust Rhinos: 608 Alverstone St. Winnipeg, MB R3G 2B9; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 3)
      - Sociable! Dust Rhinos L*I*V*E, Dust Rhinos; Recorded live May 10th and 11th at the West End Cultural Center, Winnipeg, Manitoba; 1 copy; Origin: Recorded live May 10th and 11th at the West End Cultural Center, Winnipeg, Manitoba; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 3)
      - Up Your Kilt, Dust Rhinos; Executive Producer; Brandon Friesen Produced by Dust Rhionos & Rob Shallcross, Engineered by Rob Shallcross & Paul Scinoca, Mixed by Paul Scinocca, Mastered by Darren Johnston, Recorded at Studio 11, Winnipeg, Manitoba; 1 copy; Origin: Executive Producer; Brandon Friesen Produced by Dust Rhionos & Rob Shallcross, Engineered by Rob Shallcross & Paul Scinoca, Mixed by Paul Scinocca, Mastered by Darren Johnston, Recorded at Studio 11, Winnipeg, Manitoba; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 3)
    - Echo's Children
      - From the Hazel Tree, Echo's Children; Aslan Studios; Steve Redig; Arlene "Callie" Hills; Faber, Catherine; Kirsti McElligott; 1 copy; Notes: Hand written note inside from Callie Hlils reading "Dear Harold, Here youa re, signed as requested. Thanks for including the extra postage - very thoughtful! Best wishes, Callie." The album is signed inside the liner notes, by Callie "To Harold, Best wishes, Callie Hills" and by Cat "Thanks for listening! Cat Faber". Origin: Echo's Children c/o 603 S.E. 48th Avenue, Portland, OR 97215 | Recorded at Aslan Studios, Beaverton, Oregon USA, Sound Engineer: Steve Redig, Executive Producer: Arlene "Callie" Hills, Produced by Arlene "Callie" Hills and Catherine Faber @2003. All rights reserved. Original Artwork by Kirsti McElligott @2003 All rights reserved.; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 3)
    - Julia Eclkar
      - Traveller, 1981; Ecklar, Julia; 1 copy; Origin: @1981, 2006, Julia Ecklar, traveller@filk.biz; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 5)
      - Traveller, 1981, 2006; Ecklar, Julia; 1 copy; @1981, 2006, Julia Ecklar, recording engineer Clyde Jones, Media transfer: Scott Dorsey (Kludge Audio) Digital Remastering: Adam C. Puche, Project Coordination: Eli Goldberg, Cover Illustration: Todd Hamilton, Package Design: bigwigdesign.com Thanks to Nan Burridge, Ann Cecil, Joe Ellis, Lee Gold, Todd Hamilton, Marj Ihssen, Clyde Jones, Kristopher Klover, Anne McCaffrey, Joey Shoji and Harold Stein. Origin: Eli Goldberg; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 3)
    - Emerald Rose
      - Archives of Ages to Come, 2005; Emerald Rose; Starbridge Studios; 1 copy; Notes: Signed by all the members of Emerald Rose Origin: Starbridge Studios July, 2005; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 3)
      - Celtic Crescent, Emerald Rose; Brian "Logan" Sullivan - Guitar, Vocals, Arthur Hinds - Guitar, Bodhran, Vocals, Clyde Gilbert - Bass, Percussion, Vocals, Larry Morris - Pennywhistle, Percussion, Vocals; 1 copy; Notes: There are two copies of the liner notes in the case. Origin: Brian "Logan" Sullivan - Guitar, Vocals, Arthur Hinds - Guitar, Bodhran, Vocals, Clyde Gilbert - Bass, Percussion, Vocals, Larry Morris - Pennywhistle, Percussion, Vocals; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 3)
      - Emerald Rose, Random Factors Music; 1 copy; Origin: Random Factors Music, Torrance,CA; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 3)
    - February Sky
      - Goldenrod, February Sky (Phil Cooper & Susan Urban); 1 copy; Notes: Yes, we know that CDs don't have sides. But with the 21st Century attention span being somtimes a bit short, we have provided a possible place where the listener can take a break and listen to the second "side" later. Origin: FS 03 februarysky.com; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 5)
      - Time-Honored Pathways, February Sky; Phil Cooper; Susan Urban); 1 copy; Notes: Hand written mini-post-it on the front says Harold Stein Origin: Susan Urban and Phil Cooper; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 5)
    - Bernd Felsberger
      - Brernd Felsberger - Live! Recorded live in Germany, Strange Phenomena Tour 2000, Felsberger, Bernd; 1 copy; Notes: Possibly purchased via Michael Liebmann who is credited as making sales of Felsberger's CDs in America in the liner notes. Origin: -; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 3)
    - Will Felton
      - Star Cool, Felten, Will; Ramwa Records, P.O. Box 1388, Elkhart, IN 46515; 1 copy; Notes: Hand signed note inside CD case addressed to Eli (almost certainly Eli Goldberg) Origin: Ramwa Records, P.O. Box 1388, Elkhart, IN 46515; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 3)
    - Leslie Fish
      - Skybound, 2006; Fish, Leslie; Random Factors 3754 W. 170th Street, Torrance,CA 90504-1204; 1 copy; Origin: @2006 Random Factors 3754 W. 170th Street, Torrance,CA 90504-1204; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 3)
      - Avalon is Risen, 2012; Fish, Leslie; Prometheus Music; 1 copy; Notes: Produced by Kristoph Klover Origin: Prometheus Music; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 5)
    - Dene Foye
      - For the Love of Haggis, 2014; Foye, Dene; Recorded, Engineered and Mastered by Rich Biotheton at Ace Recording, Austin, Texas; 1 copy; Origin: Recorded, Engineered and Mastered by Rich Biotheton at Ace Recording, Austin, Texas; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 5)
    - Gallamor the Bard
      - Gather Day, 2004; Macdonald, Steve; Thin Ice Studios; 1 copy; Origin: Recorded and mixed June, 2004, Thin Ice Studios; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 3)
      - Drive By Barding, 2006; Macdonald, Steve; Thin Ice Studios; Dodeka Records; 1 copy; Origin: Recorded March 2006, Thin Ice Studios, Mixed April 2006 Dodeka Records; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 3)
    - Denise Gendron
      - Make a Difference, 2007; Gendron, Denise; 1 copy; Origin:; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 5)
      - Seriously, 2014; Gendron, Denise; Many thanks to Dan Hendrix; Producer, Musician, Friend. Photo and Cover Dseign by Benjamin Flythe,; 1 copy; Origin: Many thanks to Dan Hendrix; Producer, Musician, Friend. Photo and Cover Dseign by Benjamin Flythe,; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 6)
    - Ghost of a Rose
      - Plaid & Personal, 2009; Ghost of a Rose; Recorded at Kristi Cros Studios; 1 copy; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 5)
    - Joe Giacoio
      - I Love Hamburgers, 2015; Giacoio, Joe; Romantic Devil Records; 1 copy; Origin: Romantic Devil Records; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 5)
      - I Sing the Body Acoustic, Giacoio, Joe; Romantic Devil Records; 1 copy; Origin: Romantic Devil Records P.O. Box 6284, Somerset, NJ 08875; genreform: Commercial CD (Box 3)